(this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]=this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(t,o,e){},14:function(t,o,e){},16:function(t,o,e){"use strict";e.r(o);var n=e(1),i=e.n(n),s=e(4),a=e.n(s),r=(e(13),e(5)),c=e(6),p=e(8),l=e(7),d=(e(14),e(2)),h=e(0),u=0,m=function(t){Object(p.a)(e,t);var o=Object(l.a)(e);function e(){var t;return Object(r.a)(this,e),(t=o.call(this)).next=function(){u+=1,t.setState({details:d[u]})},t.previous=function(){u-=1,t.setState({details:d[u]})},t.quit=function(){document.getElementById("quiz-cont").style.display="none"},t.state={details:d[u]},t}return Object(c.a)(e,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"quiz-parent",children:Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"quiz-cont",id:"quiz-cont",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{id:"quiz-container",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"head",children:"Question"}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-num",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("p",{id:"numbers",children:[u+1," of 15"]}),Object(h.jsx)("p",{id:"question",children:this.state.details.question})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"options-container",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"option-cont-1",children:[Object(h.jsx)("button",{id:"opt-1",children:this.state.details.optionA}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{id:"opt-2",children:this.state.details.optionB})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"option-cont-2",children:[Object(h.jsx)("button",{id:"opt-3",children:this.state.details.optionC}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{id:"opt-4",children:this.state.details.optionD})]})]})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"controls",children:[Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.previous,id:"prev",children:"Previous"}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.next,id:"next",children:"Next"}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:this.quit,id:"quit",children:"Quit"})]})]})})}}]),e}(n.Component);var b=function(){return Object(h.jsx)(m,{})},f=function(t){t&&t instanceof Function&&e.e(3).then(e.bind(null,17)).then((function(o){var e=o.getCLS,n=o.getFID,i=o.getFCP,s=o.getLCP,a=o.getTTFB;e(t),n(t),i(t),s(t),a(t)}))};a.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)(b,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),f()},2:function(t){t.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"Which of the following is not an operating system?","optionA":"Windows","optionB":"Linux","optionC":"Oracle","optionD":"DOS","answer":"Oracle"},{"question":"When was the first operating system developed?","optionA":"1948","optionB":"1949","optionC":"1950","optionD":"1951","answer":"1950"},{"question":" Which of the following is the extension of Notepad?","optionA":".txt","optionB":".xls","optionC":".ppt","optionD":".bmp","answer":".txt"},{"question":"What else is a command interpreter called?","optionA":"prompt","optionB":"kernel","optionC":"shell","optionD":"command","answer":"shell"},{"question":"What is the full name of FAT?","optionA":"File attribute table","optionB":"File allocation table","optionC":"Font attribute table","optionD":"Format allocation table","answer":"File allocation table"},{"question":"What is the mean of the Booting in the operating system?","optionA":"Restarting computer","optionB":"Install the program","optionC":"To scan","optionD":"To turn off","answer":"Restarting computer"},{"question":"Banker\'s algorithm is used?","optionA":"To prevent deadlock","optionB":"To deadlock recovery","optionC":"To solve the deadlock","optionD":"None of these","answer":"To prevent deadlock"},{"question":"When you delete a file in your computer, where does it go?","optionA":"Recycle bin","optionB":"Hard disk","optionC":"Taskbar","optionD":"None of these","answer":"Recycle bin"},{"question":"Which is the Linux operating system?","optionA":"Private operating system","optionB":"Windows operating system","optionC":"Open-source operating system","optionD":"None of these","answer":"Open-source operating system"},{"question":"What is the full name of the DSM?","optionA":"Direct system module","optionB":"Direct system memory","optionC":"Demoralized system memory","optionD":"Distributed shared memory","answer":"Distributed shared memory"},{"question":"What is the full name of the IDL?","optionA":"Interface definition language","optionB":"Interface direct language","optionC":"Interface data library","optionD":"None of these","answer":"Interface definition language"},{"question":"What is bootstrapping called?","optionA":"Cold hot boot","optionB":"Cold boot","optionC":"Cold hot strap","optionD":"Hot boot","answer":"Cold boot"},{"question":"What is the fence register used for?","optionA":"To disk protection","optionB":"To CPU protection","optionC":"To memory protection","optionD":"None of these","answer":"To memory protection"},{"question":"Which of the following is a single-user operating system?","optionA":"Windows","optionB":"MAC","optionC":"Ms-Dos","optionD":"None of these","answer":"Ms-Dos"},{"question":"Which of the following is not application software?","optionA":"Windows 7","optionB":"WordPad","optionC":"Photoshop","optionD":"MS-excel","answer":"Windows 7"}]')}},[[16,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.01f7fb53.chunk.js.map